<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MBA01</string>

    <string name="txt01">1.	<u><b>Specific Knowledge and Skills:</b></u> Each student should obtain specialized
        knowledge and skills for the creation of value through
        integrated operations and distribution of goods, services, and information.
    </string>
    <string name="txt02">2.	<u><b>Communication:</b></u>Each student can effectively
        communicate, either written or oral.
    </string>
    <string name="txt03">3.	<u><b>Ethical Reasoning &amp; Global Context:</b></u>Each student can effectively present
        information orally.
    </string>
    <string name="txt04">4.	<u><b>Problem Solving &amp; Information Technology:</b></u>Each student can work through the
        problem solving process using information technology to identify a problem, evaluate soluctions, and devise an
        innovative strategy to achieve a desired goal.
    </string>
    <string name="txt05">The goal of our Staff is to help students prepare, plan,
        and perform to graduate our program by providing knowledge, resources, and support.
    </string>

    <string name="txt06">
        The MBA Student Ambassadors are a group of student leaders dedicated to representing the MBA program
        at California State University San Bernardino.
    </string>
    <string name="txt07">1. The fostering of international and intercultural exchange amongst a diverse
        business student body.</string>
    <string name="txt08">2.	The ability to generate internship opportunities for our business students.</string>
    <string name="txt09">3.	The promotion of career development.</string>
    <string name="txt10">4.	Establishing a network of local, national and international employers.</string>
    <string name="txt11">5.	The enrichment of leadership and public speaking skills.</string>
    <string name="txt12">MBA Student Ambassador are students who have demonstrated a high potential
        for academic success, community service, fostering diversity, and responsible leadership.</string>
    <string name="txt13">Ambassadors are selected through a nomination process and are appointed by
        unanimous vote of the MBA staff.  Only MBA program students are eligible for nomination and
        Ambassadors are held to the highest standards of excellence.
    </string>
    <string name="txt14">Various events will be hosted by the Student Ambassadors throughout the
        academic year. Such events will be announce via email.</string>
    <string name="txt15">The Jack H. Brown College of Business and Public Administration values joint
        research opportunities with faculty and students. As such, each quarter the college funds a
        number of eligible candidates to be graduate and research assistants (GA). Please note: There
        are currently three offices under the College of Business that handle the hiring details
        for graduate/lab assistants.
    </string>
    <string name="drSealText">
        Dr. Craig Seal\n
        Professor\n
        MBA Director\n
        Room: JB 283
    </string>
    <string name="msD">
        Deborah Grijalva, MPA\n
        MBA Graduate Coordinator\n
        Room: JB 283
    </string>

    <string name="msAdams">
        Kasandra Adams, MBA\n
        Administrative Support \n
        Coordinator II\n
        Room: JB 283
    </string>

    <string name="mrOmar">
        Omar Palmerin\n
        Administrative Support Assistant\n
        Room: JB 283
    </string>

    <string name="passport1">
        1. <b>Leadership</b>– This passport will serve as a guide to signature activities being offered by
        the college. At the end of the academic year, MBA students who earn seven stamps on
        activities/events that represent the MBA Program Learning Goals will be awarded with an MBA
        Leadership Certificate.
    </string>

    <string name="passport2">
        2. <b>Learning Goals</b>: [click here]
    </string>
    <string name="passport3">
        3. <b>More than a Degree</b> – By completing your MBA Passport you will have the advantage of
        letting future employers know that you did more during your graduate degree than attend
        course and obtain high marks. This program will allow you to network with fellow students,
        alumni, and faculty. This is a sure way to build your resume.
    </string>
    <string name="passport4">
        <b>CBPA</b>: [Click here]
    </string>
    <string name="passport5">
        <b>MBA</b>: [Click here]
    </string>
    <string name="focusAreas">
        \n
         i.	Accounting \n
        \n
        ii.	Business Intelligence \n
        \n
        iii. Cyber Security \n
        \n
        iv.	Entrepreneurship \n
        \n
        v. Finance \n
        \n
        vi.	Management \n
        \n
        vii. Marketing Management \n
        \n
        viii. Global Supply Chain Management \n
        \n
        ix.	MBA Online Professionals \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="GradePoints">Grade points:\n
    A: 4.00, A-: 3.70 \n
    B+: 3.33, B: 3.00, B-: 2.70 \n
    C+: 2.30, C: 2.00, C-: 1.70 \n
    D+: 1.30, D: 1.00, D-: 0.70, F: 0.00
    </string>
    <string name="contact01">Ask Question / Make a Comment:\n
    *= required fields</string>
    <string name="appointment01">Fill out this form to request an appointment:\n
        *= required fields</string>
    <string name="advising01">Fill out this form to ask for advising:\n
    *= required fields</string>
    <string name="gpaCalc">Insert units and grade for each of your class:\n
    *= required fields</string>
    <string name="instruction"><b>Instructions:</b> Only click in the event that you are attending.
    The staff members will enter a passcode for you to submit your information.</string>
    <string name="warningNote"><b>Note*:</b> please double check your information before
    clicking submit button. Make sure you enter correct studentID.</string>
    <string name="checkEvent"><b>Note*:</b> please log out before checking with other studentID.</string>

    <string-array name="units">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="grade_points">
        <item>grades</item>
        <item>A</item>
        <item>A-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>C+</item>
        <item>C</item>
        <item>C-</item>
        <item>D+</item>
        <item>D</item>
        <item>D-</item>
        <item>F</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
